INFO



Name

Kim Lien Truong



(+61) 449 909 077



kimtruong1999@gmail.com

LINKS



Portfolio

kim-t-designer.github.io



LinkedIn

linkedin.com/in/kim-t-designer

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages

Python, Java, C#, HTML, CSS, Javascript, Arduino, p5.js, SQL

Software

SAP HXM Suite, 3DS Max, Adobe Creative Suite (Photoshop, Illustrator, After Effects), Figma, Balsamiq Mockups, Unity Game Engine

Industry Knowledge UX/UI Design, Interaction Design, Web Design, Design Processes and Methods, Agile Thinking

SOFT SKILLS

Leadership

Developed through co-leading CSIRO's Data61 Vacation Scholar research project, Max Potential Leadership Program as both a mentee and a coach, and university projects.

Collaboration

Developed through working with diverse roles such as software developers, HCI researchers and designers as well as diverse backgrounds during an international exchange research project in Shanghai, China.

Proactivity

Demonstrated through taking every opportunity to improve personal skills and to get involved in the local community through volunteering. Will apply expertise beyond what is required as demonstrated through pharmacy assistant role.

KIM TRUONG

DESIGNER | DEVELOPER | CONSULTANT

Summary

I am currently working as an Associate Technical Consultant in the Practice for SAP HXM team, taking over support technician roles as a SuccessFactors consultant and learning how to build HRISs from scratch. My interdisciplinary experience with research projects allows me to be flexible in whatever role I have in my team.

WORK EXPERIENCE

DXC Associate Technical Consultant 2022-CUR

> All-rounder role in consulting, involving constructing documents for clients, resolving tickets for SF LMS configurations, and communicating with clients alongside more experienced consultants.

2020-2021 CSIRO Data61 Vacation Scholar

> C# Developer and Interaction Designer role at UNSW's Extended Perception and Interaction Centre (EPICentre). Co-lead a research project exploring Virtual Reality and its applications in Gamification of the Cyber-security

space using the design process.

2015-2020 **PNW Pharmacy Assistant**



EDUCATION

2018-2022 The University of Sydney

Bachelor of Design Computing/Bachelor of Advanced

Studies (Information Systems)

TAFE NSW 2016

NSWTLTU102A Work as a Peer Tutor

NSWTLTU101A Develop Strategies to Tutor Peers HLTAID001 Provide Cardiopulmonary Resuscitation



VOLUNTEER WORK

	2021	Max Potential Leadership Program Community Coach
	2021	The University of Sydney Peer Mentor
þ	2019-2021	Sydney University Experience Designers Multimedia Sub-committee
þ	2019-2020	Sydney University Pop Culture Society Women's Officer

2018-2019 Sydney University Experience Designers

Projects Executive The Centre For Volunteering

2016 Cert I in Active Volunteering



REFERENCES

Dr Luke Hespanhol | Professor in the School of Architecture, Design & Planning | The University of Sydney luke.hespanhol@sydney.edu.au

Dr Tomasz Bednarz | UNSW's EPICentre & CSIRO's Data61 Tomasz.Bednarz@data61.csiro.au